Arthur J. Cain Papers 1945-1988 Mss.Ms.Coll.63
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1945-1988; 33 boxes; 16.25 linear feet
  - Krimbas, Costas B., 1977-1987; n.d.; 21.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Anthropology; Conferences and symposia; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Genetics -- Snails; Invitations; Lectures, public speaking; Mayr, Ernst; Requests for reprints; Travel -- Greece; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Zoology -- Nomenclature
  - Kristensen, Thomas K., 1983 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kroupa, Oldrich, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kuttner, R.E., 1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kwon, Oh Kil, 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lack, Andrew, 1987 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lack, David, 1964-1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lack, Elizabeth, 1979 (Box Series I-15)
  - Ladkin, Peter W., 1985 (Box Series I-15)
  - Laird, Marshall, 1954 (Box Series I-15)
  - Laiser, I.E., 1967 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lam, Paul K.S., 1987 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lamotte, Maxime, 1971-1985 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lampel, E.J., 1961; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Lamprey, Hugh, 1963-1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lancaster, Osbert, 1986 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lane, Philip, 1977-1985 (Box Series I-15)
  - Langford, Anthony S., 1978-1979 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lanyon, Peter G.H., 1964-1973; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Larwood, Gilbert, 1974-1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lascelles, Peter, n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Laurent, Goulven, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Leach, Louisa, 1965-1966 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lee, P.M., 1974-1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lees, David Roger, 1971-1988 (Box Series I-15)
  - Le Guyader, H., 1985; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Leme, Jose Liuz Moreira, 1982 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lerner, I. Michael (Isadore Michael), 1961; 1.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-15)
    Editorial matters; Evolution; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Leuchars, D., 1967 (Box Series I-15)
  - Levi, Claude, 1981-1985 (Box Series I-15)
    Harel, M.
  - Levin, D.A., 1971 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lewis, C.S., 1945-1946 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lewis, Geoffrey A., 1964-1982 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lewis, Hal, 1975-1984 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lewontin, Richard C., 1981; 1.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-15)
    Requests for reprints
  - Leyhausen, Paul, 1978; 1980; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Lighthill, James, 1979 (Box Series I-15)
  - Liley, N. Robin, 1958-1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lindberg, David R., 1988 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lindley, Mary, 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lindroth, Carl H., 1979 (Box Series I-15)
  - Linley, J.D., 1973 (Box Series I-15)
  - Linsley, Robert, 1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Little, Colin, 1984-1987 (Box Series I-15)
  - Livingstone, Katharine, 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lloyd, David, 1969 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lloyd, J.R., 1963-1964 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lock, J.B., 1969 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lomnicki, Adam, 1980 (Box Series I-15)
  - Longstaff, Barry C., 1976-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Loosjes, F.E., 1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lostao, Carlos Ma., 1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lovtrup, S., 1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Low, Rosemary, 1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lowe, Frank A., 1979-1980 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lu, Zhang, 1985-1986 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lubchenco, Jane, 1976-1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lund, Henry A., Jr., 1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Luxton, Malcolm, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lynch, Richard, 1986 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lynn-Evans, Julian, 1979 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lyon, Mary F., 1986 (Box Series I-15)
  - McAnuff, J.W., 1961-1962 (Box Series I-16)
  - McClellan, Patrick, 1985 (Box Series I-16)
  - McClintock, David, 1975 (Box Series I-16)
  - McConnell, Rosemary, 1959-1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - McDonald, Grace, 1958-1960 (Box Series I-16)
  - Macdonald, J.D., 1953 (Box Series I-16)
  - Macdonald, William B., 1979; 1985 (Box Series I-16)
  - McElhone, M.J., 1979 (Box Series I-16)
  - Macfadyen, Amyan, 1972-1985; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - McFarland, Valerie A., 1971 (Box Series I-16)
  - McFarlane, Donald A., 1977-1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mackenzie, Gordon A., 1981-1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mackie, George O., 1967-1971 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mackintosh, A.G., 1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - McLachlan, Athol, 1966-1977 (Box Series I-16)
  - McLannahan, Heather, n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Maclean, D.J., [1966?] (Box Series I-16)
  - McLeod, H.D.C., 1964 (Box Series I-16)
  - McMillan, Jonathan R., 1979 (Box Series I-16)
  - McMillan, Nora F., 1977-1985; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Macnair, Mark, 1982-1986 (Box Series I-16)
  - McNiven, Peter, 1970 (Box Series I-16)
  - McWhirter, Kennedy G., 1971-1974 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maddox, John, 1969-1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - Majerus, Michael E.N., 1982-1986 (Box Series I-16)
  - Malcolm, W.M., 1970 (Box Series I-16)
  - Malhotra, Sandeep K., 1981 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mallet, James, 1985-1986 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mallon, Jack, 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mancey, David, 1978 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mandahl-Barth, G., 1987 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mani, G.S., 1981-1984 (Box Series I-16)
  - Manning, Aubrey, 1973; 1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Marcus, Eveline, 1974; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Marron, Patricia, 1975 (Box Series I-16)
  - Marshall, Elsie, 1984 (Box Series I-16)
  - Martin, D.C., 1958-1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Martin, Robert D., 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Marvdashti, Abdolreza, 1984-1986; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Mass, Virginia Orr, 1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Masters, Roger P. (Box Series I-6)
  - Mather, Patricia, 1980 (Box Series I-16)
  - Matsakis, [?], 1978 (Box Series I-16)
  - Matthews, Phillip, 1984-1985; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Mattingly, James, 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mattingly, Peter F., 1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maul, G.E., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maxwell, Robin, 1981 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maxwell, Tom R.A., 1970-1971 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maxwell, W.L., 1972 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mayor, D., 1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - May, Robert M., 1976-1986 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mayer, A.M., 1976-1977 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maynard Smith, John, 1973-1984 (Box Series I-16)
    -See also Ser.I, Rosen, Brian R.
  - Mayr, Ernst, 1949-1986; 3 folders (Box Series I-16)
    American Museum of Natural History; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Genetics -- Invertebrates; Genetics -- Snails; Haldane, John Burdon Sanderson; Oxford University; Population genetics; Sheppard, Philip M.; Travel -- Europe; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Zoology -- Invertebrates
    - Folder #1, 1949-1965 (Box Series I-16)
      Edmondson, W.T.
      Pickford, Grace
    - Folder #2, 1966-1978 (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #3, 1979-1986 (Box Series I-17)
  - Medawar, Peter B., 1973-1984; 16.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-17)
    Biographical and personal data; Cancer, chemotherapy; Evolution; Lectures, public speaking; Population genetics; Requests for reprints; Sheppard, Philip M.; Zoology -- Classification; Zoology -- Gastropods
  - Melville, John W., 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Menge, Bruce A., 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Menge, Jane Lubchenco (Box Series I-17)
    -See Ser.I, Lubchenco, Jane
  - Mettam, Chris, 1986 (Box Series I-17)
  - Michener, Charles D., 1962 (Box Series I-17)
  - Middleton, Roger Clive, 1980-1981 (Box Series I-17)
  - Migos, Athanasius, 1981 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mildner, Paul, 1981 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miles, Simon, 1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miller, Jan, 1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miller, Peter, 1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miller, Suzanne Lawrenz, 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Millett, S.A., 1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Millott, Norman, 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mills, Derek, 1980 (Box Series I-17)
  - Milne, Dorothy, 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Milroy, Dominic, 1984-1985 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mirza, M.R., 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mitchell, Paul, 1987-1988 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mittwoch, Ursula, 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Monaghan, Pat (Box Series I-17)
    -See Ser.I, Armstrong, Roy
  - Monger, G., 1982 (Box Series I-17)
  - Monod, Théodore, 1970-1980 (Box Series I-17)
  - Montague, Jennifer, 1963 (Box Series I-17)
  - Montgomery, Ian, 1975-1979 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moon, Kelvin K., 1974 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moore, Angela, 1981 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moore, James R., 1972-1987 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moran, Paul M., 1973 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mordan, Peter, 1974-1988 (Box Series I-17)
    -See also Ser.I, Morris, Solene
  - Moreau, R.E., 1957-1970; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Morgan, G.R., 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morgan, Peter, 1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morgan, Phillip, 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morris, Bryn, 1978; 1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morris, Solene, 1985-1987 (Box Series I-17)
    Mordan, Peter
  - Morton, Brian, 1986-1987 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morton, J.K., 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moss, W. Wayne, 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mottershead, G.S., 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mouëza, M., 1977-1979 (Box Series I-17)
  - Munro Fox, H., 1966 (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, J.J., [Jr.], 1957-1985; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, Neil, 1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Musiba, Charles, 1987 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mussett, Alan, 1978 (Box Series I-17)
  - Myers, Greg, 1984-1985 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mylonas, M., 1985-1986 (Box Series I-17)
  - Naggs, Fred, 1984-1985 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nathan, Kathleen R., 1967 (Box Series I-18)
  - Naylor, Ernest, 1981-1986 (Box Series I-18)
    -See also Ser.I, Acuña, Luis Treviño
  - Neck, Raymond, 1973 (Box Series I-18)
  - Needham, A.E., 1974 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nei, Masatoshi, 1985-1986 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nelson, J. Bryan, 1972 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nevo, Eviator, 1970-1982 (Box Series I-18)
  - Newberry, Keith, 1971-1972; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Newmark, Peter, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Newswanger, Stephen, 1978 (Box Series I-18)
  - Newth, David R., 1978 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nichols, David, 1967-1988 (Box Series I-18)
  - Noakes, Kenneth W., 1971 (Box Series I-18)
  - Noble, Leslie, 1981-1987; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Norris, Adrian, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-18)
  - Norton, Trevor A., 1986 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nugent, Zoann J., 1982-1985; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Oberling, J.J., 1976-1986 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ochando, Bernard, 1978 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Donald, Peter, 1968-1984; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Donovan, Peter, 1986 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Grady, [?], 1959 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Hara, Ken, 1985 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Kane, J.G., 1970-1979 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oliff, W.D., n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Oliver, Anthony J., 1983 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oliver, P. Graham, 1986 (Box Series I-18)
  - Olson, Jane, 1974 (Box Series I-18)
  - Omodeo, Pietro, 1981 (Box Series I-18)
  - Onions, T.G., 1967 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oosterhoff, Lucy M., 1972 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ortiz, E[ugenio], 1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Osborne, Jeremy, 1980 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ostler, A., 1963 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Toole, Christopher, 1970; 1983 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ovenden, Jenny R., 1987-1988 (Box Series I-18)
  - Owen, David, 1981-1985; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Owen, Denis F., 1964-1971; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Owen, J., 1977 (Box Series I-18)
  - Owens, Simon, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxford, Geoffrey S[tuart], 1971-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxley, A.H., 1968 (Box Series I-18)
  - Paget, Oliver E., 1978-1983 (Box Series I-18)
  - Palacio, Francisco J., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Palmer, A. Richard, 1985 (Box Series I-18)
  - Palmieri, Margaret, 1977 (Box Series I-18)
  - Panchen, Alec L., 1977 (Box Series I-18)
  - Pantin, C.F.A., 1960-1963 (Box Series I-18)
  - Papagounos, I., 1985 (Box Series I-18)
  - Parker, H.W., 1953 (Box Series I-18)
  - Parkes, A.S., 1967-1968 (Box Series I-18)
  - Parkin, David T., 1964-1980; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Parr, Michael J., 1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Parsons, Peter A[ngas], 1977-1983 (Box Series I-18)
  - Partridge, Linda (Box Series I-18)
  - Paterson, Hugh E., 1977-1978 (Box Series I-18)
  - Patterson, Bryan, 1976 (Box Series I-18)
  - Patterson, Colin, 1978 (Box Series I-18)
  - Pau, Richard, 1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Paul, Chris R.C., 1976-1979 (Box Series I-18)
  - Peake, J.F., 1968-1978 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pearson, Howard, 1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Peberdy, J.F., 1975 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pedder, Ian J., 1968-1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Perkin, Michael R., 1974 (Box Series I-19)
  - Perkins, Keith III, 1984 (Box Series I-19)
  - Perrins, Chris M., 1957-1987 (Box Series I-19)
  - Perry, R.J.O'B., 1986 (Box Series I-19)
  - Peterson, Charles H., 1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Petit, Richard E., 1984-1985 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pettitt, Charles, 1969-1978 (Box Series I-19)
  - Petuch, Edward, 1982 (Box Series I-19)
  - Phillips, John Guest, 1966-1975 (Box Series I-19)
  - Phillipson, John, 1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Phipps, John, 1964-1965 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pickersgill, Barbara, 1975-1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pickford, Grace (Box Series I-19)
  - Piearce, Trevor G., 1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pigott, C. Donald, 1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pitcairn, T.K., 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pitcher, Wallace S., 1971-1977 (Box Series I-19)
  - Platt, Austin P., 1977; n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Ploog, Detlev (Box Series I-19)
  - Plumb, A., 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Poll, E., 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pollitt, Richard, 1988 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pollock, M., 1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pomeroy, D.E., 1979-1980 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pontin, A. John, 1978-1979 (Box Series I-19)
  - Poole, Trevor, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pop, Victor, 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Por, F.D., 1977 (Box Series I-19)
  - Porter, John, 1982 (Box Series I-19)
  - Potter, E.A., 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Potter, W.G., 1968 (Box Series I-19)
  - Potts, G.R., 1981 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pratt, Joe D., 1982-1983 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pratt, Vernon, 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pratt, William L., 1982-1983 (Box Series I-19)
  - Preston, Julia Carter, 1980 (Box Series I-19)
  - Prezant, Robert S., 1982 (Box Series I-19)
  - Price, David J., 1982 (Box Series I-19)
  - Price, Paul, 1961-1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Prieto, Carlos E., 1982 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pringle, John W.S., 1962-1968 (Box Series I-19)
  - Proctor, M.H., 1964 (Box Series I-19)
  - Proctor, Sue C., 1978 (Box Series I-19)
  - Provine, William B., 1984-1988, n.d.; 2 folders (Box Series I-19)
    American Philosophical Society; Biographical and personal data; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Evolution; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Ford, Edmund Brisco; Genetics -- Snails; History of biology, especially genetics; Mayr, Ernst; Medawar, Peter Brian; Oxford University; Population genetics; Preservation of historical materials; Sheppard, Philip M.; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Wright, Sewall; Zoology -- Nomenclature
    - Folder #1, 1984-1988 (Box Series I-19)
      Dobzhansky, Theodosius
      Wright, Sewell
    - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Puri, G.S., 1970-1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pusey, Joan, 1979 (Box Series I-19)
  - Race, Elizabeth, 1982 (Box Series I-20)
  - Radburn, V.P., 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Radford, D.J., 1978-1979 (Box Series I-20)
  - Raffaelli, David G., 1974-1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rahim, M.A., n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Rainford, R.A., 1964-1967 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ramos, M. Angeles, 1979-1985 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rands, E.B., 1973-1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ranger, K.F., 1963-1964 (Box Series I-20)
  - Raven, Peter H., 1984-1985 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rawlings, Peter, 1976-1977 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rayburn, Keith, 1986 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rees, Christopher J.C., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rees, M., 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rees, Malcolm, 1982 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rees, T.D., 1979 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reid, David G., 1985-1986 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reilly, Elizabeth, 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reimchen, Thomas E., 1969-1988; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Reveal, James L., 1972-1973 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reynoldson, T.B., 1974; 1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Richards, Paul W., 1968-1969 (Box Series I-20)
  - Richardson, Al, 1972-1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Richardson, Bonham C., 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Richardson, C. Len, 1977-1984 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ride, W. David L., 1987 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ridley, Mark, 1982-1983 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rieger, Reinhard M., 1980-1981 (Box Series I-20)
  - Riley, Gordon, 1980 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ritterbush, Philip C., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rix, Anne, 1963 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roach, D.K., 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roberts, David, 1973-1986 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roberts, H. Wallace, 1977-1981; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Roberts, Michael B., 1982-1986 (Box Series I-20)
    Rev[erend]
  - Roberts, Michael B.V., 1969-1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robertson, Alan, 1979 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robertson, Forbes, 1977 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robertson, J. Graeme, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robertson, Robert, 1975-1988 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robins, Michael, 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robinson, Michael H., 1982 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rochford, Julian, 1985 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rodgers, Michael G., 1979 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roff, John C., 1977-1978 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rogers, Stella, 1964 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rooke, Diana, 1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rosen, Brian R., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-20)
    Maynard Smith, John
  - Rosewater, Joseph, 1978-1979; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Ross, Keith F.A., 1973-1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rössler, Otto E. (Box Series I-20)
  - Rostron, J., 1977 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roth, Barry, 1976-1980 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roth, Vincent, 1959 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rothschild, Miriam, 1968-1988 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rowley, Ian, 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roy, Ashok, 1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Royama, Tomo, 1967-1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rudman, P., 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Runham, Norman W., 1974-1982 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ruse, Michael, 1972-1986; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Russell, George, 1976; 1980; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Russell, Malcolm, 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Russell, W.M.S., n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Russell-Hunter, W.D., 1980-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Ryan, Lee, 1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rydzewski, W., 1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ryland, J.S., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Sacchi, Cesare F., 1974-1986 (Box Series I-21)
  - Safriel, Uriel N., 1980 (Box Series I-21)
  - Salomonsen, Finn, 1973 (Box Series I-21)
  - Salt, George F., 1980 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sampson, Elizabeth, 1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sands, W.A., 1966 (Box Series I-21)
  - Santiago, Antony, 1981 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sapienza, Carmen, 1983 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sarjeant, William A.S., 1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - Savage, Jay M., 1983 (Box Series I-21)
  - Saver, Jeffrey L., 1981 (Box Series I-21)
  - Scali, Valerio, 1975 (Box Series I-21)
  - Schleidt, W.M. (Box Series I-21)
  - Schlichter, Lyanne, 1977 (Box Series I-21)
  - Schmidt, H., 1974 (Box Series I-21)
  - Schmidt, John P., 1986 (Box Series I-21)
  - Schmidt, W., 1977 (Box Series I-21)
  - Schopf, Thomas J.M., 1974 (Box Series I-21)
  - Schwaner, Terry D., 1983 (Box Series I-21)
  - Scott, Nora, 1975 (Box Series I-21)
  - Scott, Vicki, 1978 (Box Series I-21)
  - Scriven, Nigel, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-21)
  - Scudder, Geoff G.E., 1975-1977 (Box Series I-21)
  - Seaborg, David, 1978 (Box Series I-21)
  - Secker, H.L. (Box Series I-21)
  - Seed, R., 1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - Seeley, Robin Hadlock, 1986 (Box Series I-21)
  - Segerstrale, Ullica, 1986 (Box Series I-21)
  - Seghers, Benoni H., 1977 (Box Series I-21)
  - Serpell, James A. Folder #1, 1973-1975 (Box Series I-21)
  - Serpell, James A. Folder #2, 1976-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-21)
  - Seyd, E.L., 1974 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shanin, Teodore, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shapiro, Arthur M., 1979 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sheals, J. Gordon, 1973-1975 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shelstone, Alan, 1972 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shepley, Alan [V.], 1962-1963 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sheppard, Anthony, 1978 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sheppard, Philip M., 1953-1980; 3 folders (Box Series I-21)
    Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Evolution; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Genetics -- Cats; Genetics -- Snails; Huxley, Julian; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Lectures, public speaking; Population genetics; Publication; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Travel -- Solomon Islands; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Folder #1, 1953-1960 (Box Series I-21)
      -See also Ser.I, Dommée, Bertrand
      -See also Ser.I, Douglas, Ann
      -See also Ser.I, Harvey, Paul
    - Folder #2, 1961-1966 (Box Series I-21)
    - Folder #3, 1967-1980; n.d. (Box Series I-21)
  - Shine, John, 1978 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shkolnik, Amiran, 1976-1977 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shorrocks, Bryan, 1968-1982 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shutt, M[argaret] S., 1972 (Box Series I-21)
  - Shuttleworth, John, 1972 (Box Series I-21)
  - Sibley, C.G., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simla, David, 1959 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simpson, Beryl B., 1981 (Box Series I-22)
  - Simpson, George Gaylord, 1954-1984; 18.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-22)
    Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Simpson, George Gaylord. 80th birthday; Evolution; Publication; Publication -- Animal Species and their Evolution; Requests for reprints; Teilhard de Chardin, Pierre
  - Simpson, Rod D., 1983 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sinclair, Anthony R.E., 1961-1978; n.d. (Box Series I-22)
  - Singh, Ram, 1959 (Box Series I-22)
  - Skibinski, David, 1979 (Box Series I-22)
  - Skinner, Sam W., 1983 (Box Series I-22)
  - Slack-Smith, Shirley M., 1983 (Box Series I-22)
  - Slatkin, Montgomery, 1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, Christopher, 1987 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, Christopher J., 1979 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, D[avid] A.S., 1976-1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, J.E., 1974 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, J. Eric, 1975-1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, Jean M., 1972 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, K.V.G., 1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, Martin, 1980 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, Shelagh, 1979 (Box Series I-22)
  - Smith, Sydney, 1968-1980 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sneath, P.H.A., 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Snow, David W., 1970-1971 (Box Series I-22)
  - Snow, R.B., 1968 (Box Series I-22)
  - Snowden, Richard, 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sofianos, John, 1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Solem, Alan, 1978-1985 (Box Series I-22)
  - Solhoy, Torstein, 1981-1984 (Box Series I-22)
  - Soong, Michael, 1985-1986 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sortwell, Andrew, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-22)
  - Southern, H.N., 1967-1983 (Box Series I-22)
  - Southern, Roger, 1986-1987 (Box Series I-22)
  - Southwood, T.R.E., 1983 (Box Series I-22)
  - Speed, R.M., 1976 (Box Series I-22)
  - Spencer, Geoffrey, 1986 (Box Series I-22)
  - Spencer, Penelope J., 1980 (Box Series I-22)
  - Speyer, Stephen E., 1986 (Box Series I-22)
  - Spiess, Eliot B., 1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Spight, Tom M., 1970-1972 (Box Series I-22)
  - Spilsbury, Richard Leslie, 1985 (Box Series I-22)
  - Squire, G.M., 1972 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stam, Peter, 1979-1981 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stanisstreet, Martin, n.d. (Box Series I-22)
  - Stanley, Steven, 1977 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stanton, W.I., 1987 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stearn, William T., 1972-1981 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, n.d. (Box Series I-22)
  - Steel, David, 1987 (Box Series I-22)
  - Steiner, F.N., 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stelfox, A.W., 1969-1971 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stevcic, Z., 1971-1973 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stevens, P.F., 1988 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stevenson, Jim, 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stewart, D.R.M., 1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stileman, Richard, 1972-1974 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stockwell, Elisabeth, 1960-1962 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stonehouse, Bernard, 1969 (Box Series I-22)
  - Storer, Ronald, 1986 (Box Series I-22)
  - Strong, Donald R., 1985 (Box Series I-22)
  - Stuttard, Robin, 1986 (Box Series I-22)